lcdtvbuyingguide.com 2016-03-15

# LCD TV Buying Guide: flat screen tv ordering FAQ & Tips

**Updated January, 2012**

## CEAG’s Privacy Notice

By visiting [LCDtvbuyingguide.com](https://lcdtvbuyingguide.com/), [plasmatvbuyingguide.com](http://plasmatvbuyingguide.com/), or [3d-tvbuyingguide.com](http://3d-tvbuyingguide.com/) you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

We value your privacy and it is important to us. We strive to provide you with the best reviews possible on current day electronics products – that's CEAG Inc. company group of websites objective. Following is our Privacy Policy to help you feel at ease that your search experience on our websites is secure and private. This policy does not govern information you might provide to us by means other than search or website use. Due to the fact that the Internet is Global in nature, any information you provide to us or that we collect may be held in countries other than the United States and other than that in which you contacted us from. By using our websites, you effectively consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

## Information you Submit To Us Voluntarily:

You may visit our websites and utilize our services without identifying yourself or revealing any information that would help anyone personally identify you. However, if you wish to comment on your pages or further provide information to us about who you are in order to receive our e-mail newsletter then we collect and use that information for the purposes of contacting you. We may also collect some added information about you when you visit certain features or areas of our websites or services or the pages of certain of our partners when you interact with offers and advertisements or when and if you contact us for support. Other examples include when you log into the Services with your account, when you complete a survey, or when you enter promotions. Lastly, you may choose to submit an alias, biographical information, email, photos or any other information that you would like to share with other users of the Services such as a comment through our comments sections. All of this information is termed by this policy as Shared Information. 

## Information we Collect Automatically

We may automatically collect your IP address when visiting our web sites. This information helps us to better understand how our users are utilizing our services. It helps us better understand you, our customer. This IP information may also be collected by our Partners and Advertisers when utilizing their services or clicking on a promotion from them. Other information we may automatically collect is your browser type, access time, and the web page you entered our site from, the we page you leave our site for and the individual web pages on our sites that you enter when utilizing our web sites. This data we term as Utilization Data. We may use such Utilization Data to diagnose issues and problems with our services, servers, and software and to gather demographic data. Our third party advertising networks and our server services also provide us with reports and data that inform us about the number of ads presented and clicked on in a manner than does not personally identify any individual or user. 

## Information Sharing

Except as described by a promotion or service or in this Privacy Policy, we will never share your personal Utilization Data, personal information, or shared information with any third party without your permission. We may from time to time share non-personal Utilization Data to enable third parties who administer advertisements or Services to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you. We will not share any information or data that would enable an advertiser or third party to be able to personally identity you. 

We may share aggregated Utilization Data with third parties, particularly demographic data. We will not share any aggregated Utilization Data that will enable any personal identification of you. 

In the event that we enter into a relationship with a service provider that collects information necessary for transactional use (i.e. credit card transaction) we disclose only the user information necessary for such service providers to perform those services and require that the information be held confidential by them. 

We reserve the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us, to share any Utilization Data in the following circumstances as required by law: In direct response to subpoenas, for court orders, or for legal process. Also to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. In the event we have reason to believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property. In the event we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding significant abuse of the Services’ infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as obvious spam, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information). To companies under our control or if we are acquired by or merged with another company. 

## Information Deemed as Public

Any information by a user as public authorizes us implicitly to treat it as public and share the information publicly. This applies to comments, posts by you, message boards, discussion rooms, forums and the like. By utilizing these areas, you understand and agree that this public information may be accessed by anyone and that anyone may use, disclose any information that you post to public areas of the web sites. 

## Cookies

We may set and access cookies on your computer from time to time. The cookie may be used to identify your browser type. The information collected from cookies may help us to better serve our users. Browsers from users may be set to automatically block cookies, however you will not be able to sign in to specific services if the cookies setting is blocked. 

## Advertising

Other companies may advertise their services on our web sites from time to time. These companies may collect and use click information, browser type, access time, and any information you provide if and when clicking on the advertisement. In the event the advertisers collect information through cookies, pixel tags, beacons or the like, use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policy policies. We do not share our cookie information with Advertisers. None of our Advertisers may collect personal information about you through us. 

## Modifying and Deleting Personal Information

You may delete any personal information previously provided to us by accessing your profile and making the preferred changes there, or opting out by choice from any communication that we send to you (i.e. e-mail newsletter). Otherwise we will maintain Utilization Data in our database only when we are required to do so by law. 

## Security of Utilization and Personal Information

We have implemented and use security measures to help protect your personal and user information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access or disclosure. While Internet data transmission security cannot be guaranteed as 100% secure, we do implement security measures to protect this data and information. 

## Links to other Web Sites or Services

We are not responsible for the privacy practices web sites or services other than our own. We urge our users to review the privacy practices of any other web sites they may link from ours – especially before entering any personal information. 

## Policy Regarding Children's Use

We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s Internet activities. Our web sites and services and those services of our third party advertisers are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target the Services to children under the age of 13. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will inform you of such change by posting a notice on relevant areas of the web sites and on this Privacy Policy notice page. Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date stated therein. 

## Questions

Please visit and fill out our [Contact Form](https://lcdtvbuyingguide.com/contact-form.php) should you have any questions.
